Let's log in Wix.
go to "edit".
" Insights"
and now these are the posts we have
published so far. When you see this,
click, and you'll see "manage posts.
" You'll go to the back stage of
it.. These are the published one.
You can see the published dates, views,
comments, likes, and also the categories
I set... duplicate any of it (the post).
It will automatically go to this
"copy of blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah. "This happens automatically..
Go to Claude.
Upload the Playbook and your
article and paste this prompt.
I have shared this prompt with you.
This prompt is about Let Claude
know the playbook, which is
the guidance of your blog.
So let Claude read the
guidance and your article.
The second one is your article.
And then it will create a HTML file.
You can just click it and see the result.
See it is not perfectly as we want, but
the layout is very similar as we had.
Okay.
go back to Wix.
This is the copy of what we just made.
Do the copy and paste.
That's it.
However, it is tricky
while you copy and paste.
Please make sure the format like, this,
the font from Claude is not correct.
so just copy, comment C, and paste.
And the second one, paste it.
It doesn't follow our rule.
It doesn't create any
of this, gray paragraph.
It's okay.
Make it flexible.
Just copy this with the
green quotes one to here.
See the font changed, so you have to
be careful when you pasting it because
sometime the format may not goes right.
So see this, 18 font size.
Just make it into 18 manually.
Posting needs to be very careful,
but don't too stress 'cause.
The layout already is here.
After we copy paste all the text , we
have to ask Claude to generate
these images into JPG for us by
giving a snapshot and showing the
reference to them (Claude or GPT).
Okay, how to upload an image?
Go click the "+" button, image.
upload media.
and click the one we want.
For example, if this is the
one we want, just add to page.
That's it.
And make it size to our original size.
It will make the resolution looks better.
If the mark goes wrong.
Go to alignment, left again.
This is just the system problem.
Let's say we finish all the content.
Go here.
AI tools, settings.
SEO are the most important.
Go to AI tools.
And meta text.
This will boost the SEO.
This is very important
and just create AI text.
A meta description you can create by ai.
You can use the AI here
or chat GBT to help you.
This will appear on the feature
and also these are very important.
Please ask AI to assist you.
This will help the searching
engines to search this article.
if you realize one of your article,
fits some trending keywords in
Abu Dhabi you need to modify them.
This expert excerpt.
This is also very important...
in Abu Dhabi, you need to modify them.
This expert excerpt, this is also very important.